https://www.morrisonsecurity.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentWhat Information Do We Collect?Any data provided via form or otherwise to this website shall be considered eligible for collection and segmentation.EmailWe actively maintain an email program in order to communicate with our customers and job seekers. All email subscriptions made via this website require a double opt in on behalf of the subscriber to ensure no there is no untoward behavior in our collection of subscriber emails.Advertising and TrackingWe may and most likely are at this very moment leveraging a myriad of targeting, tracking and analytic solutions in order to market our company. This includes cookies, site analytics (provided by Google), as well as tracking pixels from Google, Facebook and other digital platforms. If you are uncomfortable with this, we encourage you to install an ad-block plugin, turn off javascript (though that will in fact break portions of this site), or simply leave. You are welcome to browse our site anonymously.Financial DataThis site processes no transactions and does not store nor collect payment information of any sort.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer, to any outside parties, your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on 01/10/20Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.www.morrisonsecurity.com
12334 S. Keeler Avenue
Alsip, IL 60803
USA
info@morrisonsecurity.com
708 389-2400
What We DoSecurity Services
Nationwide Emergency Service
Loss Prevention
Visit Us:Chicago
12334 S Keeler Ave,
Alsip, IL 60803Las Vegas
1909 Weldon Pl,
Las Vegas, NV 89104Miami & Orlando
7600 Southland Blvd #100,
Orlando, FL 32809Visit Us:Chicago
12334 S Keeler Ave,
Alsip, IL 60803Miami & Orlando
7600 Southland Blvd #100,
Orlando, FL 32809Las Vegas
1909 Weldon Pl,
Las Vegas, NV 89104ILLINOIS LICENSE NUMBER
IDFPR: 102-000296 – NOTE: ILLINOIS SERVICES UNDER THIS LICENSE NUMBER ARE FOR FIREARMS TRAINING INSTRUCTION
IDFPR: 122-000807 – LICENSED PRIVATE SECURITY CONTRACTOR AGENCYFLORIDA LICENSE NUMBER FDACS: B2700305 – LICENSED PRIVATE SECURITY AGENCYNEVADA LICENSE NUMBER PILB: 1137 – NOTE: NEVADA SERVICES UNDER THIS LICENSE NUMBER ARE FOR PRIVATE PATROL SECURITY SERVICES ONLY (ARMED AND UNARMED SECURITY OFFICERS)
Start typing and press enter to search
Search …
